var questions=[
	{
		question:"[1]. When was the anonymous group found?",
		answer:"2003",
		options: ["2001","2003","2008","2009"]
	},

	{
		question:"[2]. When Did the first Known Anonymous attack launched?",
		answer:"2008",
		options: ["2001","2003","2005","2008"]
	},

	{
		question:"[3]. What is the platform that anonymous first formed?",
		answer:"4chan",
		options: ["Reddit","Omegle","4chan","9GAG"]
	},

	{
		question:"[4]. Who is the novel character is used for the anonymous mask?",
		answer:"Guy Fawkes",
		options: ["Guy Fawkes","Robert Castesby","Edward Fawkes","Thomas Percy"]
	},


	{
		question:"[5]. Which of the following is not a anonymous attack?",
		answer:"Operation Thunderbolt",
		options: ["Operation Payback","Operation Titstorm","Operation Chanology","Operation Thunderbolt"]
	},

	{
		question:"[6]. What is the name used for the first known anonymous attack?",
		answer:"Operation Chanology",
		options: ["Operation Chanology","Bank of America Attack","Justice for MegaUpload","Operation Sony"]
	},

	{
		question:"[7]. Nearly how many members are there in the anonymous group worldwide?",
		answer:"Unknown",
		options: ["1500","2000","Unknown","None of Above"]
	},

	{
		question:"[8]. Who was the billionaire that anonymous were threatening recntly?",
		answer:"Elon Musk",
		options: ["Bill Gates","Elon Musk","Jeff Bezos","Jack Ma"]
	},

	{
		question:"[9]. Which of the following is not a part from anonymous tagline?",
		answer:"We are the justice",
		options: ["We are the leigon","We are the justice","We do not forget","We do not forgive"]
	},

	{
		question:"[10]. Which institute of the following is not affected by 'Operation Payback?'",
		answer:"American Express",
		options: ["Visa","MasterCard","MPAA","American Express"]
	},
];
